My team and I turn coaches, authors, and
influencers into money-making machines.
I livestream on the
internet one hour a day.
It's called Funnel Hacking Live.
Funnel hacking is where I go online like
a consumer and walk your
entire customer journey.
I find you online.
I really like what you have to say.
I'd love to buy something from you.
75 percent of the time, I can't.
You send me to your Facebook
page or your Instagram page.
You don't have a website.
You don't have a product.
Here's what that costs you.
The smallest package any client of
mine sells is ten thousand dollars.
So when your opportunity comes and you get in front
of a large audience with nothing to offer them,
you just left hundreds of
thousands of dollars on the table.
I fix that.
We package your intellectual
property and we drive the
attention you generate to a
website you own and control.
So the next time you get a speaking
engagement or your next big opportunity,
you can capitalize on it.
I wrote a book about our process.
It's called Attention To Dollars.
Attention plus your
product equals dollars.
There are three ways to work with us.
Do it yourself, done with
you, or done for you.
You're in the right place.
Have a look around.
I look forward to talking.